Register of the Christopher Temple Emmet Papers 1913-1974
Hoover Institution Archives
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1936-1973
  - "Appeasement Imperils Peace," July 21, 1945
  - "Rankin and the Communists," July 30, 1945
  - "Owen J. Lattimore," August 22, 1945
  - "Rough Preliminary Survey of Possible Topics and Speakers for Freedom House Post-Election Institute on New York City," August 30, 1945
  - "The Palestine Crisis," November 1945
  - "Memorandum on Hurley Incident," December 19, 1945
  - "Chiang Kai-shek," 1946
  - "Hitler's Spirit Still Lives," 1946, (with others)
  - "Memorandum on the State Department Blue Book on the Argentine in the Light of the Commonweal Artices," 1946(?)
  - Review of Stegner, Wallace, One Nation, January 1946
  - "The Problems of Sharing and Controlling the Atomic Bomb," February 1946
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, February 7, 1946
  - "Our Argentine Blunder," February 8, 1946
  - "Our Future Argentine Policy," February 15, 1946
  - "The Communist Crisis in China and in France: Will Chiang Go the Way of de Gaulle?" February 16, 1946, (with J. B. Powell)
  - "World Freedom of Information: Only Key to Peace," April 8, 1946
  - "Manchurian Manifesto," May 16, 1946, (with others)
  - Tragedy of a People: Racialism in Czecho-Slovakia, June 1946, (with others)
  - Letter to the editor, Florida Catholic, July 20, 1946
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, August 2, 1946
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, August 26, 1946
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, October 11, 1946
  - "Answer to Questionnaire on Germany for Die Tat, Zurich, Switzerland," October 31, 1946
  - "Verdict on Nuremberg," November 22, 1946
  - "Why the Republican Landslide," December 1946
  - "The Moral Basis of the Peace," December 6, 1946 (Box 108)
  - "Is Disarmament Possible?" December 16, 1946
  - "An Answer to Henry Wallace," 1947
  - "Background of the Cable to Bevin," 1947
  - "Comparison of Italian Treaty with Atlantic Charter," 1947(?)
  - "Confidential Memorandum on the Significance of the Berle Proposal to Delay Action on the Italian Peace Treaty," 1947(?)
  - Destruction at Our Expense: How Dismantling Factories in Germany Helps Inflation in the United States and Sabotages the Marshall Plan, 1947, (with Fritz Baade)
  - "Draft of Resolution Submitted to Annual Meeting of Polish-American Congress," 1947(?)
  - The Land of the Dead: Study of the Deportations from Eastern Germany, 1947, (with others)
  - "Memorandum on the Status of the Dismantling Problem in Relation to Inter-Allied Agreements, After Failure of the London Conference," 1947(?)
  - Men Without the Rights of Man: A Report on the Expulsion and Extermination of German Speaking Minority Groups in the Balkans and Prewar Poland, 1947(?), (with others)
  - "Vote Liberal," 1947(?)
  - "Iran and Henry Wallace," January 4, 1947
  - "'By Their Fruits Ye Shall Know Them,'" March 1947
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, March 2, 1947, (with others)
  - "Confidential Memorandum on the Vital Importance of Defeating Ratification of the Italian Treaty in the Light of President Truman's Message on Greece," March 28, 1947
  - "The Muddled Conservative," March 29, 1947
  - "Unlimited Bomb Inspection Necessary," March 29, 1947
  - "Lilienthal and Unity," April 4, 1947
  - Testimony before U.S. Senate Foreign Relations Committee, May 2, 1947
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, July 20, 1947, (with others)
  - "An Appeal for Aid to Britain Now," August 1947, (with others)
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, October 23, 1947
  - "Appeal Against Dismantling German Factories Now," November 13, 1947, (with others)
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, November 18, 1947, (with others)
  - "Who Won the Election?" 1948
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, March 7, 1948
  - "The Last Chance for Peace: A Plan to Save Italy from the Fate of Czechoslovakia and So Preserve America's Lifeline in the Mediterranean," March 15, 1948
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, April 23, 1948
  - "The Mundt-Nixon Bill," June 25, 1948
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, September 15, 1948
  - "Draft of Statement on China," October 25, 1948, (with Natalie Wales Paine)
  - "Citizens Group Reveals Communsist Affiliations of Dean of Canterbury," November 15, 1948, (with others)
  - Letter to the editor, various newspapers, December 23, 1948
  - "Proposed Solutions for 'Diplomatic' Problems Which Have Arisen Over Carnegie Hall Meeting," 1949
  - "Supplementary Comments After Bishop Oxnam's Speech Accepting the Churchman Good-Will Award," 1949(?)
  - "Unchallanged Statements Made by Louis Nizer on a Coast-to-Coast Network on CBS People's Platform, November 19, 1949, in a Debate with Walter Litchfield, Former Civilian Affairs Officer under General Clay in Berlin," 1949(?)
  - "Memorandum to All National Groups Who Are Sending Delegations to the Common Cause Rally on May 5th at Carnegie Hall," April 23, 1949
  - Speech, Common Cause Freedom Rally, New York, May 5, 1949
  - "Memorandum on the Navy-Air Force Controversy," October 1949
  - "The Background of Pearl Harbor: A Refutation of Admiral Theobald's Thesis," 195?
  - "Should Communist China Be Admitted to the UN?" 195?
  - "Should We Veto Communist China?" 1950
  - "Is There a Revival of German Nationalism?" February 1950
  - "Memorandum on German Refugee Problem," February 1950
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, April 2, 1950
  - "Memorandum on a New York Preview of the Battle for Berlin," May 1950
  - "An American View of British Policy in China," July 1950
  - "Deutschland Wird Verteidigt" (Germany Will Be Vindicated), August 4, 1950
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, November 1, 1950
  - "McCarran's Blunderbuss," November 3, 1950
  - "Letter to a European Friend on the American Elections and Their Relation to China," November 14, 1950
  - "The Alternative to Appeasement: Neither Munich nor Hiroshima," December 9, 1950 (Box 109)
  - "Common Cause Replies to Mr. Hoover," December 24, 1950
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, December 27, 1950
  - "An Analysis of General MacArthur's Utterances from the Time of His Dismissal to His Testimony before the Senate Committee," 1951(?)
  - "Possible Consequences in the Soviet Cease-Fire Proposal," 1951(?)
  - "Common Cause Appeals for Use of the UN Veto Against Communist China," January 29, 1951, (with Natalie Wales Paine)
  - Letter to the editor, America, February 1, 1951
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, March 18, 1951
  - "Statement on MacArthur's Dismissal," April 15, 1951, (with Natalie Wales Paine)
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, April 30, 1951
  - "Appeasement in Korea," July 1951
  - "Let the Facts Alone: A Liberal's Critical Examination of the Lack of Foundation of Alsop and Related Liberals' Attacks on McCarran Security Investigation," September 21, 1951
  - "Misgivings in Asia About the Japanese Peace Treaty," 1952(?)
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, January 24, 1952
  - "Summary Statement on the Impending Crisis," January 29, 1952, (with Arthur McDowell)
  - "Memorandum on I.R.C. Problems," February 9, 1952
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, April 19, 1952, (with others)
  - Letter to the editor, Washington Post, April 24, 1952, (with others)
  - "Confidential Memorandum on German-American Relations: Why No Neutrality Seems Possible," May 1952
  - "Koje: Conspiracy to Wreck the Truce," June 2, 1952
  - "Zwischenbilanz im Amerkanischen Wahlkampf" (Interim Report on the American Election Campaign), June 26, 1952
  - Letter to the editor, New Leader, July 18, 1952
  - Review of Miller, Merle, The Judges and the Judged, August 1952
  - Speech, German-American Club, Munich, August 27, 1952
  - "Statement on Behalf of Aid Refugee Chinese Intellectuals, Inc., before President's Commission on Immigration and Naturalization," October 1, 1952
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, November 16, 1952
  - "Memorandum on the Indian Cease-Fire Proposal," November 23, 1952
  - Speech, Amerika-Gesellschaft, Hamburg, December 8, 1952
  - "China and Communism," 1953
  - "The Indian Cease-Fire Plan Re-Examined," 1953(?), (with David Martin)
  - "Memorandum on the South Korean Release of the Prisoners of War," 1953(?)
  - "A Profile of President James B. Conant of Harvard, New High Commissioner to Germany," 1953(?)
  - "Statement on Korean Prisoner of War Issue," 1953(?)
  - "Statement Which Could Be Made by Baltic and Eastern European Leaders-in-Exile, Warning Against the Dangers in a New Non-Aggression Pact with Soviet Russia," 1953
  - "Lebensbild des Neuen US-Hochkommissars fuer Westdeutschland Dr. James Conant" (Sketch of the New U.S. High Commissioner for West Germany, Dr. James Conant), February 12, 1953
  - "China and the U.N.: The Acid Test of Anglo-American Unity," March 1953
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, May 9, 1953, (with Hans Kohn and Norbert Muhlen)
  - "Anglo-American Differences Over China and Korea," May 18, 1953
  - "Memorandum on Inter-Allied Crisis Over Korea and the Proposed Conference with Malenkov," May 20, 1953
  - "The Anglo-American Rift," May 30, 1953
  - "Memorandum for Guidance of Delegates to Copenhagen Conference and for Use Here in Promoting the American Council on NATO," August 1953
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, November 10, 1953
  - "Memorandum on the Approaching Diplomatic Crisis Focusing on the Admission of Communist China to the U.N.," December 1953
  - "Neglected Aspects of the White Case," December 1953 (Box 110)
  - "Ost-West Handel als Politisches Kernproblem" (East-West Trade as the Central Political Problem), 1954
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, January 15, 1954
  - "The President and the Atom," February 12, 1954
  - Letter to the editor, Encounter, March 1954
  - Review of Buckley, William F., Jr., and L. B. Bozell, McCarthy and His Enemies, May 15, 1954
  - "McCarthy-Army Probe: First Fortnight," May 22, 1954
  - "Primer of American Policy in the Cold War," June 1954
  - "Confidential Memorandum on the Failure of the Bills to Restore German Private Property," August 1954
  - "Recommendations for Different Steps at Government and Private Levels to Overcome Anglo-American Misunderstandings," August 1954
  - Speech, September 24, 1954
  - "Draft for Statement on U.N. Admissions by Committee of One Million," 1955(?)
  - "Purposes of the American Friends of Vietnam," 1955
  - "Reflections on the Problem of Communist China and the Defense of Formosa," 1955
  - "Why a Committee of American Friends of Vietnam Must Be Organized," 1955(?)
  - Review of Allport, Gordon W., The Nature of Prejudice, February 1, 1955
  - "Statement on United States Policy Against Admission of Communist China to the United Nations," February 9, 1955, (with Harold L. Oram)
  - "Memorandum Showing Necessity to Revive Committee of One Million," February 12, 1955
  - "Memorandum on Anglo-American Differences Over Formosa," February 14, 1955
  - "Memorandum on the Impression of Foreign Minister Martino on Meet the Press, " April 6, 1955
  - "Draft for an Open Letter to Mr. Attlee to be Circulated for Signature Among Liberal and Labor Groups," April 19, 1955
  - "Draft for Statement on Negotiations by Committee of One Million April 30, 1955
  - "Draft of Proposed New Statement on the Prisoner of War Issue," June 25, 1955
  - "Memorandum on the Geneva Conference," July 28, 1955
  - "A Reply to Ellen Hammer's 'The Struggle for Indo-China Continues,'" August 1955 (Box 111)
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, August 28, 1955
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, October 5, 1955
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, October 29, 1955
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, November 5, 1955
  - "Outline of Facts and Chronology on German Misunderstandings of the 'Radford Memorandum,'" 1956
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, January 26, 1956, (with others)
  - Letter to the editor, Commonweal, February 6, 1956
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, February 16, 1956, (with others)
  - "Trend of American Public Opinion on Vietnam," March 1, 1956
  - "American Political Situation as of March 7, 1956," March 7, 1956
  - Speech, American Friends of the Captive Nations Liberation Rally, New York, May 25, 1956
  - "Why the West Is Losing," June 1956
  - Speech, Polish American Congress, July 6, 1956
  - Letter to the editor, New Leader, July 9, 1956
  - "Tenth Anniversary, Execution of Drazha Mihailovich," July 16, 1956, (with others)
  - Letter to the editor, New York Post, September 23, 1956
  - "Comment on Article by Former Ambassador George Kennan in August 1956 Issue, Harper's Monthly, 'Overdue Changes in Our Foreign Policy,'" October 1956
  - "A Comment on the Debate Over a Positive vs. Negative Approach to the Fight Against Communism," October 1956
  - "The American Reaction to the Hungarian Revolution," October-December 1956
  - "Report of Activity on the Party Platforms by the American Friends of the Captive Nations," October 1, 1956
  - Letter to the editor, New York Herald-Tribune, November 5, 1956
  - "Satellites Break Away," November 10, 1956
  - "Appeal for Ten Point Program to Stop Soviet Aggression in Hungary Including an Emergency Session of Congress to Consider the Adoption of Economic and Other Sanctions," November 12, 1956, (with Monsignor John Balkunas)
  - "Memorandum on the Madison Square Garden Rally," November 14, 1956
  - Letter to the editor, America, November 17, 1956
  - "Statement Approved by Executive Committee of American Friends of the Captive Nations," November 27, 1956
  - Letter to the editor, Time, December 8, 1956
  - Letter to the editor, Saturday Review, December 10, 1956
  - Letter to the editor, Christian Science Monitor, December 13, 1956
  - "Christian A. Herter," 1957
  - "Lessons of the Hungarian Revolution," 1957
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, 1957
  - "Memorandum on Background and Implications of the Polish Crisis," 1957
  - "Memorandum on Tito's Visit and the A.F.C.N. Ad," 1957(?)
  - "Should We Support Titoism in Eastern Europe?" 1957
  - "Does Hungary Increase the Danger of War?" January 1957
  - "Memorandum on the Protests Against the Visits of King Saud and Marshal Tito," February 8, 1957
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, February 25, 1957, (with others)
  - "Comment on Erich Ollenhauer's Visit to the United States," March 1957
  - "To President Eisenhower and the American People on the Anniversary of Hunarian Independence," March 6, 1957
  - "Outline of Thesis," March 13, 1957
  - Speech, National Conference on Spiritual Foundations, 3d, Washington, March 18, 1957
  - "Memorandum on Some of the Reasons Behind Congressional Opposition to Aid to the Gomulka Government," March 23, 1957
  - "Memorandum Outlining Our Financial Problems and Opportunities," March 27, 1957, (with Raphael Malsin)
  - "Our Lost Chance in Hungary," May 1957 (Box 112)
  - "Should U.S. Have Helped Hungary More?" May 15, 1957
  - "Progress Report to All Organizations Which Have Approved the Plan to Reconvene the U.N. General Assembly to Consider the Special Report on Hungary," May 16, 1957
  - "Memorandum on U.N. Project," May 21, 1957
  - "Our Second Choice in Hungary," speech, Council Against Communist Aggression dinner, Washington, June 12, 1957
  - "Memorandum to Press, Radio and T.V.," June 25, 1957
  - Testimony before U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee, June 26, 1957
  - Speech, plenary meeting, Assembly of Captive European Nations, June 28, 1957
  - "Memo on Khrushchev's Triumph," July 5, 1957
  - Review of Berle, A. A., Jr., Tides of Crisis, August 3, 1957
  - "Can Hungary Still Be Saved?" November 1957
  - "Report on U.S. Reaction to Sputnik and Other Developments," November 15, 1957
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, November 18, 1957
  - Letter to the editor, Life, December 12, 1957, (with others)
  - Letter to the editor, Die Zeit, December 26, 1957
  - "Memorandum on Life Editorial on Berlin in December 15 Issue," 1958
  - "Memorandum on Problem of Distribution of Volume II of Hungary under Soviet Rule, " 1958(?)
  - "The Neglected Testimony of Refugees from Eastern Europe," 1958(?)
  - "The Present Role of Nationalism in Eastern Europe," 1958
  - "Proposed Joint Statement on Cultural Exchanges," 1958, (with Julius Epstein)
  - Review of Fejto, Francois, La Verite sur l'Affaire Nagy, 1958
  - "Should Germany Be Neutralized? A Reply to Kennan," 1958(?)
  - "Volume II of Hungary under Soviet Rule, " 1958(?)
  - "The Acheson-Kennan Debate," speech, Lexington Democratic Club, January 24, 1958
  - Letter to the editor, New York Post, January 29, 1958
  - Letter to the editor, The Reporter, February 6, 1958
  - "Report on the Release of Statements by Dean Acheson and by Former Ambassador Conant, etc., in Reply to George Kennan," February 28, 1958
  - Letter to the editor, National Review, March 30, 1958
  - Review of Hoover, J. Edgar, Masters of Deceit, April 5, 1958
  - "Hungary and the Summit Conference," April 18, 1958
  - "Statement on the Summit Conference," May 7, 1958, (with others)
  - "If De Gaulle Take Over: A Prediction," May 15, 1958
  - "Debate on Nuclear Tests," May 20, 1958
  - "Further Reflections on De Gaulle," May 20, 1958
  - Letter to the editor, The Nation, July 7, 1958
  - "Proposed Action on U.N. Middle East Meeting," August 5, 1958
  - Letter to the editors, New York Journal-American and World Telegram, August 11, 1958
  - Untitled, October 4, 1958
  - Speech, plenary session, Assembly of Captive European Nations, October 23, 1958
  - "Pertinent Facts, Points to Stress, and Answers to Objections on the Question of Expelling the Hungarian Puppet Delegates from the U.N. General Assembly," November 1958 (Box 113)
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, November 19, 1958
  - "Background Memo on Relation between the Threat to Berlin and Hungary," December 2, 1958
  - Letter to the editor, various newspapers, December 12, 1958, (with others)
  - "Report on Our U.N. Campaign," December 30, 1958, (with Angier Biddle Duke)
  - "Brief Appraisal of the Khrushchev Visit," 1959
  - "The Concequences of the Khrushchev Visit: Peaceful Coexistence of Disaster?" 1959(?), (with David Martin)
  - Letter to the editor, Indianapolis News, 1959, (with John Balkunas and Stefan Korbonski)
  - "Questions and Answers on Berlin: Introduction," 1959(?)
  - "Why Has Nixon the Anti-Communist Suddenly Emerged as the Champion of Khrushchev's Wildest Dream: An Invitation to the U.S. Without Even Having Withdrawn the Berlin Ultimatum?" 1959
  - "Confidential Memorandum on the Dulles Press Conference Reference to the Possiblilty of Uniting Germany Without Free Elections," January 17, 1959
  - "Report on the Lessons of the Mikoyan Visit," January 23, 1959
  - "Report on Mayor Brandt's Debate on Ed Murrow's TV Program Small World, Sunday, January 25," January 28, 1959
  - "Lessons of the Mikoyan Visit," January 31, 1959
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, February 25, 1959
  - "Memorandum on Proposed Campaign to Clarify Berlin Issue in Relation to Eastern Europe," March 23, 1959
  - "Implications of Macmillan's Peace Program," March 30, 1959
  - "Memorandum on the Adenauer-Macmillan Disagreement as Publicly Revealed by Adenauer's Speech in the New York Times of April 9," April 10, 1959
  - "Letter to a Friend in Washington," April 15, 1959
  - "The Pitfalls of Negotiation," April 20, 1959
  - Letter to the editor, New Leader, May 18, 1959
  - "Memorandum on Conversation with Mr. Herter," May 20, 1959
  - "Relaxation of Tensions and Cultural Exchange: Smokescreen for Soviet Expansion," July 1959
  - "Why Adenauer Changed His Mind (or the Adenauer-Erhard Controversy)," July 1959
  - Questions and Answers to the Berlin Crisis, July 1, 1959
  - "Captive Nations Week, 1959: A Manifesto," July 20, 1959, (with Monsignor John Balkunas and Stefan Korbonski)
  - "U.S.-Soviet Relations," July 20-27, 1959
  - Letter to the editor, various newspapers, July 21, 1959, (with Monsignor John Balkunas and Stefan Korbonski)
  - "Khrushchev's Tirade Against Captive Nations Week," July 24, 1959, (with Monsignor John Balkunas and Stefan Korbonski)
  - "Memorandum on Khrushchev's Reaction to Captive Nations Week," July 24, 1959
  - "Flowers for Khrushchev?" August 1959
  - "Joint Statement on Khrushchev Visit," August 7, 1959, (with others)
  - "Why Are the USSR Negotiating? Because They Want Stability or Because They Are Preparing Further Expansion?" September 1959
  - Letter to the editor, New York Journal-American, September 9, 1959
  - Speech, New York, September 20, 1959
  - Speech, Amerika-Haeuser, Munich, Stuttgart and Hamburg, October 1959
  - "Report on Mission to Paris and London," November 12, 1959 (Box 114)
  - Speech, Assembly of Captive European Nations memorial meeting for Dr. Povl Bang-Jensen, New York, December 9, 1959
  - "American Friends of the Captive Nations Program in 1960," 1960
  - "Comparison between Stevenson Position on 1956 Atomic Tests and Eisenhower's Position Today," 1960
  - "Confidential Memorandum on Dr. Dobriansky and the Ukrainian Congress Committee," 1960(?)
  - "Democratic and Republican Conventions," 1960
  - Hungary under Soviet Rule, Volume IV, Introduction, 1960, (with Peter Zenkl)
  - "Is There a Sino-Soviet Split?" 1960, (with Suzanne Labin)
  - "Key Points in a Protest Against Khrushchev and His Quislings," 1960
  - "Memorandum on Nehru's Statement Against German Unity," 1960
  - "The New Soviet Test Ban Proposal," 1960
  - "Why the Present U.S. Defense Debate Is Not Only Indecisive but Irrevelant," 1960
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, February 8, 1960
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, February 9, 1960
  - Speech, dinner in honor of Constantin Fotitch, New York, February 13, 1960
  - "Further Notes on the Soviet Test Proposal," March 30, 1960
  - "The Berlin Question: An American View," April-May 1960
  - "Statement Approved by the Executive Committee of the American Friends of the Captive Nations for Presentation to Undersecretary of State Livingston Merchant," May 10, 1960
  - "Comment on Khrushchev's Threat to Break Up the Summit Conference," May 16, 1960
  - "Brief Summary of Conditions in the Baltic Countries," June 1960
  - "Memorandum on the Definition of 'Captive Nations,'" June 10, 1960
  - Testimony before Regional Democratic Platform Committee, Los Angeles, June 21, 1960
  - "Memorandum on Advantages of Walter Judd as Republican Vice Presidential Candidate," June 30, 1960
  - "Manifesto: Captive Nations Week, 1960," July 4, 1960, (with Monsignor John Balkunas and Peter Zenkl)
  - Testimony before Democratic Platform Committee, Los Angeles, July 7, 1960
  - "Comment on Testimony of Dr. Leo Dobriansky before Republican Platform Committee," July 20, 1960
  - Testimony before Republican Platform Committee, Chicago, July 20, 1960
  - "Questions for Senator Kennedy on Eastern Europe," August 10, 1960
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, September 1, 1960
  - "Memorandum on Kennedy and Poland," October 1960
  - "Memorandum on Appeal to Senator Kennedy," October 5, 1960
  - Speech introducing Senator Thomas J. Dodd, Harvard Club testimonial dinner, October 19, 1960
  - "A Comment on the Kennedy-Nixon Offshore Islands Debate," October 29, 1960
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, 1961 (Box 115)
  - "Manifesto for the Fifth Anniversary of the Hungarian Revolution," 1961, (with others)
  - "Memorandum on Stevenson Plan to Drop Hungary and Tibet from the United Nations Agenda as 'Cold War Issues' in Exchange for Soviet Agreement to Postpone Debate on Disarmament," 1961(?)
  - Questions and Answers on the Berlin Crisis (revised edition), 1961
  - "Report on the Political Panel," 1961
  - "Report on the Second American-German Conference," 1961